lifestylescoop.com 2019-05-13

# Privacy Policy - Lifestylescoop

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which lifestylescoop collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.lifestylescoop.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by lifestylescoop.com

_Personal identification information_

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, social security number. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

_Non-personal identification information_

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

_Web browser cookies_

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

_How we use collected information_

Lifestylescoop may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

– To Improve Customer Service Information You Provide Helps Us Respond To Your Customer Service Requests And Support Needs More Efficiently.  
– To Personalize User Experience We May Use Information In The Aggregate To Understand How Our Users As A Group Use The Services And Resources Provided On Our Site.  
– To Improve Our Site We May Use Feedback You Provide To Improve Our Products And Services.  
– To Process Payments We May Use The Information Users Provide About Themselves When Placing An Order Only To Provide Service To That Order. We Do Not Share This Information With Outside Parties Except To The Extent Necessary To Provide The Service.  
– To Run A Promotion, Contest, Survey Or Other Site Feature To Send Users Information They Agreed To Receive About Topics We Think Will Be Of Interest To Them.  
– To Send Periodic Emails We May Use The Email Address To Send User Information And Updates Pertaining To Their Order. It May Also Be Used To Respond To Their Inquiries, Questions, And/Or Other Requests. If User Decides To Opt-In To Our Mailing List, They Will Receive Emails That May Include Company News, Updates, Related Product Or Service Information, Etc. If At Any Time The User Would Like To Unsubscribe From Receiving Future Emails, They May Do So By Contacting Us Via Our Site.

_How we protect your information_

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

_Sharing your personal information_

We do not sell, trade, or rent users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

_Disclosure of information to third parties_

Lifestylescoop may share non-PII with third parties for a variety of reasons, including to enable our platforms or partners to deliver targeted advertisements that we or they believe will be of most interest to you. Hot Fashion, may also disclose your information to third parties when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Release of your personal data pursuant to this section, to any person or entity under any circumstances shall be based on a determination made solely by us, exercising our own discretion, permission for which is expressly granted by you to us in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Lifestylescoop may share Non-PII and PII with entities controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Lifestylescoop. Lifestylescoop may transfer information to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or other corporate change.

Lifestylescoop does not control third parties collection or use of your information to serve interest based advertising. However, you can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) by accessing the link[ http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

_Changes to this privacy policy_

Lifestylescoop has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

_Your acceptance of these terms_

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

_Contacting us_

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: info@bidder.media
